Guide to the School of Art, Yale University, Memorabilia
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Art, Yale University, memorabilia
1949-2013
RU 399
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.27
(7 boxes)
The material consists of printed material, posters and a scrapbook of newspaper clippings documenting activities and events of the Yale School of Art and the Yale School of Art & Architecture.
Yale University. School of Art
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 20-H (YRG 20-H), Audio-visual materials and memorabilia documenting the Yale School of Art.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The material consists of printed material, posters and a scrapbook of newspaper clippings documenting activities and events of the Yale School of Art and the Yale School of Art & Architecture.
Art schools; Posters; Scrapbooks; Yale University. School of Art and Architecture; Yale University. School of Art
- Ephemera, 1998; Accession 1998-A-126
  - Ephemera, 1998 (Box 1)
- Scrapbook documenting the School of Fine Arts and the School of Art, 1949-1957; Accession 2001-A-117
  - Scrapbook documenting the School of Fine Arts and the School of Art, 1949-1957 (Box 1)
- Memorial program for Andrew Forge, 2002; Accession 2003-A-069
  - Program, 2002 November 11 (Box 1)
  - Audiocassette, 2002 November 11 (Box 1)
- Spring student exhibition poster, 2003; Accession 2003-A-146
  - Spring student exhibition poster, 2003 (Folder 1)
- Poster, catalog and invitation for Walker Evans centennial exhibition, 2003 2003; Accession 2004-A-125 (Box 1)
  - Poster, catalog and invitation for Walker Evans centennial exhibition, 2003 (Box 1)
- School of Art Spring 2008 lecture series poster, Accession 2009-A-071
  - Spring 2008 lecture series poster (Box 1)
- Alton S. Tobey press packet, 2008; Accession 2009-A-172
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Alton S. Tobey 90th birthday celebration press packet, 2008 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes bio, photos, and portfolio.
- Memorial program for Alvin Eisenman, 2013 October 26; Accession 2017-A-049
  - Program, 2013 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 1)